# **Aung Si Min Htet**

M.S. Student

Address Jeonju, South Korea

Phone +821021751105

E-mail andy@jbnu.ac.kr

Pursuing Master's degree focused on Computer Vision and Deep Learning. Experienced software engineering and software development with several programming languages and frameworks including Java, Python and Laravel. Al researcher with hands-on experience transforming research ideas into real-world applications using Tensorflow and Pytorch.

## **Work History**

#### 2020-08 - Current

### Research Assistant

Software Engineering Lab, Jeonbukn National University

- During my master's degree, I have worked at Software Engineering Lab of Professor Hyo Jong Lee by helping him with his research projects.
- Researched on deep learning based computer vision projects and implemented the research ideas into industry-use software systems for endusers on different platforms (android applications, windows executable programs) using end-to-end ML/DL pipelines.
- Research projects I have worked on and developed:
- 1. Pig Scale Smart Application with the use of 3D ToF sensors in mobile devices, we have researched and developed smart application that can measure the accurate weights of the pigs just by using the ToF camera of mobile devices.
- 2. Palm Vein Biometrics Authentication System I have researched and published on palm vein biometrics recognition and developed authentication system using palm vein biometrics feature which performs more secure than existing palm print and finger print recognition system. Just by using a simple NIR sensor, our window-based palm authenticator application can collect palm vein templates in contactless manner and identify the user instantly.

#### 2020-03 - 2021-04

# Senior Software Engineer

ConceptX Myanmar

- As senior Software Engineer at ConceptX Myanmar, which is leading online education platform based in Yangon, I was responsible for developing scalable and high-performance native android and iOS applications using Java, Kotlin and Swift programming languages, as well as back-end API services using PHP and Laravel framework.
- Best software development practices such as Unit Testing, architecture and design (MPV, MVC, MVVM), and agile methodologies are well practiced.
- While worked with project managers, college developers, Q.A. team to resolve technical issues and develop new features, also trained and mentored junior developers by sharing hand-on technical experiences.

- https://conceptxmm.com/
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=co.binary.conceptx

#### 2020-03 - 2021-04

## **UI/UX Designer**

ConceptX Myanmar

- Besides working as a Software Engineer at ConceptX, I have also helped them working as a front-end developer as well as designing the user interface/user experience designs for android and iOS applications, and the website.
- Helped designing the top 1 online education platform in Myanmar with useroriented, mobile-friendly and easy-to-access modern UI/UX design concepts.

#### 2018-03 - 2019-12

## **Mobile Development Lead**

Binary Tech

- As mobile development lead at Binary Tech, which is software development firm based in Yangon, I have managed small team of software engineers, and visual designers to develop and deliver several end-to-end mobile and web based software systems to meet various clients' business requirements.
- Developed and delivered more than 30 software development projects.

#### 2016-01 - 2017-12

## **Android Developer**

ETrade Myanmar

- Responsible for developing mobile responsive android applications.
- Developed native android applications using Java and Android Studio.

## **Education**

#### 2013-09 - 2018-08

# Bachelor of Science: Computer Science And Engineering

Dagon University

#### 2020-09 - Current

# Master of Science: Computer Science And Engineering

Jeonbuk National University

## **Awards**

- 2015 Grand Prize Winner at SAMSUNG Tech Institute Mobile Application Development Competition
- 2016 Korean Government Scholarship Program (KGSP)
- 2019 Global Korea Scholarship (GKS)
- 2021 Best Paper Award at 2021 International Conference on Computer Engineering and Artificial Intelligence (ICCEAI)

# **Publications**

• A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "TripletGAN VeinNet: Palm Vein Recognition Based on Generative Adversarial Network and Triplet Loss," 2021 International

- Conference on Computer Engineering and Artificial Intelligence (ICCEAI), 2021, pp. 454-458.
- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Palm Vein Identification and Verification using Deep Metric Learning," The 2022 World Congress in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, & Applied Computing (CSCE'22), 2022.
- A. S. M. Htet and H. J. Lee, "Attention Gated Residual Segmentation for Palm Vein Authentication," *The Annual Conference of Korea Information Processing Society*, 2022 (To be published).

## **Technical Skills**

Java, Kotlin, Python, PHP, Laravel, Javascript, C++, Swift, C#, Matlab, UI/UX Design, Deep Learning, Computer Vision, Tensorflow, Pytorch

# Languages

English, Korean, Burmese